Guide to the Cornell University College of Arts and Sciences records,1905-1993.
Cornell University College of Arts and Sciences records,1905-1993
- Physical Education, 1925-1944 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Semitic Languages, 1927-1931 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Policy Committee on Extension Studies, 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Education Policy Subcommittee on Language Requirements, 1945-1950 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Mathematics Proficiency - Committee to Administer Exam, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Arts - Architecture Committee, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Committee on American Studies, 1947-1950 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Ad Hoc Committees, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Proficiency in English Committee, 1946-1949 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Faculty - Trustee Committee on Fine Arts (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Educational Policy, 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Educational Policy, 1934-1935 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Educational Policy, 1935-1936 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Educational Policy, 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Educational Policy, 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Educational Policy, 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Educational Policy, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Educational Policy, 1940-1941 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Educational Policy, 1941-1942 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Educational Policy, 1942-1943 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Educational Policy, 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Educational Policy - Foreign Language, Terms of Instruction, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- College of Home Economics, 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- School of Hotel Administration (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Division of Education (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Graduate School of Education, 1931-1933 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Graduate School of Education, 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Graduate School of Education, 1934-1935 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Graduate School of Education, 1936-1943 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Graduate School, 1929-1933 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Graduate School, 1934-1944 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Astronomy Department, 1946-1952 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Chemistry Department Appointments, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Chemistry Department Appointments, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Chemistry Department Appointments, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Chemistry Department, 1949-1952 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Classics Department Appointments, 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Economics Department Appointments, 1949-1952 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Economics Department, 1948-1951 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- English Department Appointments, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- English Department Appointments, 1950-1952 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- English Department, 1949-1952 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Professor Nungezer Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Far Eastern Studies Department Appointments, 1948-1951 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Fine Arts Department Appointments, 1950-1952 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Geology Appointments, 1949-1952 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Geology Department, 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- German Literature Department Appointments, 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Government Department, 1949-1951 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Government Appointments, !948-1951 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- History Appointments, 1949-1952 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- History Department, 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Literature Department, 1947-1951 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Mathematics Appointments, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Mathematics Appointments, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Mathematics Department, 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Modern Languages Appointments, 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Modern Languages Appointments, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Modern Languages Department, 1949-1952 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Music Appointments, 1949-1952 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Music Department, 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Nuclear Studies Appointments, 1947-1951 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Nuclear Studies Appointments, 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Nuclear Studies Appointments, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Nuclear Studies Department, 1947-1949 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Nuclear Studies Department, 1949-1952 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Philosophy Department, 1947-1952 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Philosophy Department Appointments, 1949-1952 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Physics Department Appointments, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Physics Department Appointments, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Physics Department, 1949-1951 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Psychology Department, 1950-1952 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Psychology Appointments, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Romance Language Department, 1944-1952 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Sociology Appointments, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Sociology and Anthropology Department, 1950-1952 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Speech and Drama Department, 1947-1955 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Speech and Drama Department, 1950-1952 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Zoology Department, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Zoology Department Appointments, 1950-1952 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Handbook for Economics 1 - Prepared by the Instructors, 1920's (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Examination Questions - Economics 1, 2a, 1920's (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Examination Questions - Economics 67a, 67b, 1920's (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Examination Questions - Economics 54 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company Meeting Minutes, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Economics 54 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Economics 5 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Model Answers to Questions - Economics Courses (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Annual Report - Department of Modern Languages and Linguistics, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Annual Reports Department of Music, Near Eastern Studies; Philosophy, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Annual Reports - Physics, Psychology, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Arts and Sciences Unofficial Registrar’s Cards - A - Fink, Louis, Pre 1920 (Box 15)
- Arts and Sciences Unofficial Registrar’s Cards - Finkelstein, Harold - Mandelberg, Joseph, Pre 1920 (Box 16)
- Arts and Sciences Unofficial Registrar’s Cards - Mandeville, Margaret - Shuler, John David, Pre 1920 (Box 17)
- Arts and Sciences Unofficial Registrar’s Cards - Shulman, Abraham - Z, Pre 1920 (Box 18)
- Annual Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
- Annual Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 3-4)
- Annual Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 5-7)
- Annual Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Annual Reports, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 9-11)
- Annual Reports, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 12-13)
- Annual Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 14-19)
- Annual Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
- Annual Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 3-14)
- Annual Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 15-18)
- Annual Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 1-8)
- Annual Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 9-22)
- Annual Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
- Annual Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Accessory Instruction, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- [RESTRICTED] Admissions, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- [RESTRICTED] Admissions, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- [RESTRICTED] Admissions, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- [RESTRICTED] Admissions, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- [RESTRICTED] Admissions Survey, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Asian-American Coalition, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Astronomy, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Attrition, 1959-1970 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Audio-Visual, 1970-1977 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Campus Planning - Space Management, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Canisus College, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Canisus College, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Capstone, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Commmittee of Deans, 1969-1972 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Common Learning, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Commuting Course Study, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Comparative Literature - External Review, 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Continuing Education, 1975-1977 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Cornell Cinema, 1973-1981 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Cornell Days, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Corporate Relations, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Corson's Office, 1969-1975 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- COSEP Search, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- COSEP Study, 1969-1972 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- [RESTRICTED] COSEP Counseling, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- COSEP, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- [RESTRICTED] COSEP Counseling, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- [RESTRICTED] COSEP Counseling, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- COSEP, 1969-1976 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Minority Education Plan, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- COSEP Handbook, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- COSEP Admissions, 1970-1974 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- COSEP Learning Skills Center, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- COSEP Learning Skills Center, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- COSEP Learning Skills Center, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- COSEP Plan, 1970's (Box 23, Folder 10)
- [RESTRICTED] COSEP Counseling, 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- COSEP Study, 1968-1977 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- COSEP Bulletin, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- COSEP Students, 1970-1972 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Minority Education Plan, 1970's (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Africana Studies, 1968-1970 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Africana Studies and Research Center, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Counseling Meeting, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Course Evaluation, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Course Load, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Courses, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- College Proficiency Examination, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Continuing Orientation Talks, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- CO-OP Plan, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Cooperating With Other Institutions, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Cornell University Award, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Council of Student Personnel Associates, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Institutional Functioning Inventory, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Institutional Self-Study, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Cranch Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Cranch Report - Newspaper Clippings, 1971-1973 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Dance, 1973-1978 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Development Projects, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Division of Educational Opportunity, 1967-1970 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Freshman Humanities Program, 1969-1973 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Freshman Seminar Program, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Dorm Courses, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Double Registration, 1971-1973 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Dropping Courses, 1971-1974 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Duplication of Courses, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Early Evaluation, 1972-1975 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Educational Innovation, 1972-1974 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Educational Policy Committee, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Educational Policy Committee, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Educational Policy Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Educational Pollicy Committee, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Educational Policy Committee, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Educational Policy Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Educational Reform, 1971-1976 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- English Teaching Program, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Extramural Courses, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Buttrick and Danforth Fund, 1971-1980 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Becker Fund, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Buchanen Memorial Fund, 1965-1967 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Butler Fund, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Bekowitz Fund, 1960-1983 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Dean's Essay Prize, 1974-1977 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Dechert Goldring Fund, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Evans Memorial Fund, 1958-1965 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Farr Fellowship, 1957-1978 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Fullbright Act, 1947-1969 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- German Marshall Fund, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Harbison Harris Award, 1965-1972 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Hirsch Bequest, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Howard Foundation, 1972-1977 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Humanities and Social Sciences Fellowship, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Final Fall Statistics, 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- [RESTRICTED] Grades, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- [RESTRICTED] Grading, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- [RESTRICTED] Grading, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- [RESTRICTED] Grading, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- [RESTRICTED] Grading, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- [RESTRICTED] Grading, 1974-1976 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Final Fall Statistics, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- FCR Admissions, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Florida A and M University, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Fully Funded Study, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- German Students, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- Bernie Goodman, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- History and Philosophy of Science and Technology, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Human Biology Program, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Humanities Consortium, 1960-1980 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Center for the Humanities, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Center for the Humanities, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Interdisciplinary Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Inter-Institutional Cooperation, 1969-1972 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Ithaca School District, 1976-1981 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Learning Skills Center Space, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Lecture Study, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Priorities Study, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Program for Participation and Labor-Managed Systems, 1977-1987 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Religious Studies Proposal, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Religious Studies Proposal, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Search Plans, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Service Courses, 1965-1973 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Social Psychology, 1969-1974 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Social Sciences Committee for New Directions, 1966-1968 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Social Sciences Committee for New Directions, 1966-1979 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Summer work - Scholarship Program (Box 25, Folder 20)
- TA and Graduate Stipends, 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- TA Study, 1978-1984 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- University Room Scheduling, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- American Studies; Africana; Arts Quad Renovation, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Asian Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Biology, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Biophysics; Center for International Studies, 1971-1973 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Chemistry; China Program; Classics, 1971-1974 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Comparative Literature; Computer Science, 1971-1974 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Departments, 1072-1974 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Economics, 1970-1973 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Economics, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Economics, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- English, 1971-1974 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Ethnic Studies; Female Studies, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Fine Arts, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Government and German Literature, 1970's (Box 26, Folder 2)
- History and Art History, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Human Affairs Program, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Humanities, 1965-1970 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Literature, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- LASSP; Psychology; Philosophy, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Mathematics, 1972-1974 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Modern Languages, 1971-1974 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Music, 1971-1974 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Office Space - Goldwin Smith, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Religious Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Romance Studies; Russian Literature, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Romance Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Semantics, 1971-1974 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Sociology, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Teaching Assistants, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Theatre Arts; Physics, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Urban Studies, 1970-1973 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- [RESTRICTED] Correspondence: Don Randel and Philip Lewis, January 1993 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- [RESTRICTED] Correspondence: Don Randel and Philip Lewis, February 1993 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- [RESTRICTED] Correspondence: Don Randel and Philip Lewis, March 1993 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- [RESTRICTED] Correspondence: Don Randel and Philip Lewis, April 1993 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- [RESTRICTED] Correspondence: Don Randel and Philip Lewis, May 1993 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- [RESTRICTED] Correspondence: Don Randel and Philip Lewis, June 1993 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- [RESTRICTED] Correspondence: Don Randel and Philip Lewis, July 1993 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- [RESTRICTED] Correspondence: Don Randel and Philip Lewis, August 1993 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- [RESTRICTED] Correspondence: Don Randel and Philip Lewis, September 1993 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- [RESTRICTED] Correspondence: Don Randel and Philip Lewis, October 1993 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- [RESTRICTED] Correspondence: Don Randel and Philip Lewis, November 1993 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- [RESTRICTED] Correspondence: Don Randel and Philip Lewis, December 1993 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Lynne Abel "Why a Major?", no date; V-795 (Box 27)
- Carol Greenhouse, Anthropology, no date; V-796 (Box 27)
- English, no date; V-797 (Box 27)
- Arthur Bloom, Geology, no date; V-798 (Box 27)
- Isabel Hull, History, no date; V-799 (Box 27)
- Blackfoot (Blood), Linguistics, no date; V-800 (Box 27)
- Michael Morley, "Math Department Options", no date; V-801 (Box 27)
- Janet Smith-Kitner, "Why Math?", no date; V-802 (Box 27)
- Peg Unsworth, "Predictors of Success of Cornell", no date; V-803 (Box 27)